

About

Senior Professional still in the transition phase from the Oil and Gas industry to the Wind Energy industry, with more than 20 years of experience in medium and large companies, accumulating extensive expertise in Strategic Planning, Contract Management and Field Operations.

With some experience in the Blade Repair activity, now at Wind Energy, he intends to use his experience to contribute decisively to the sustainability of companies in the renewable energy sector.

- **L** +55 22 99203-7051
- marcelo.inspetor@hotmail.com
- Fagundes Varela, 123 Centro - Itaboraí - RJ

Academic Education

Instituto de Ensino Superior de São Paulo Bachelor's degree in Business Administration

2013 - 2016

Escola Técnica José Rodrigues **Mechanical Technician** 2008 - 2009

Certifications and Courses

- GWO BR Balde Rapair
- GWO BST Basic Safety Training
- GWO ART Advanced Rescue Training
- Rope Access Level 1
- ACFM Inspector
- Dimensional Inspector
- Equipment Inspector
- Industrial Painting Inspector Level 1
- Industrial Painting Inspector Level 2

MARCELO PAIVA

Painting Inspector | IRATA Rope Access Blade Repair Technician | GWO - BR / ART / BST

Professional experience

Blade Repair Technician Assistant

02/2023 - 10/2023

ADComp - Advanced Composites Solutions

Aracati Wind Farm - Ceará - Brasil

- Lightning damage
- Impact Damage
- Leading edge repairs
- Internal general repairs and web repairs

Blade Repair Technician Assistant

05/2022 - 11/2022

SGS

Mataco & San Jorge Wind Farmi - Buenos Aires- Argentina

- Lightning damage
- Impact Damage
- Leading edge repairs
- Internal general repairs and web repairs

Operations manager

06/2018 - 02/2022

TECH-INSP Óleo e Gás

Management of the company's operations at a national level, coordinating and promoting integration between the company's sectors, with emphatic action in the Commercial, Financial and Operational departments.

Direct interaction with customers, such as Petrobras, Modec, SBM and others, with the purpose of guaranteeing the full execution of activities as well as the integrity of the teams and customer satisfaction.

Contract Manager

03/2017 - 05/2018

TECH-INSP Óleo e Gás

Management of contracts with Petrobras: Class Inspection and Emerged Structures contract (UO-RIO), Naval Inspection (UO-ES), Rescue at Height and Confined Space (UO-Reduc).

Management of installation and installation maintenance teams, Rope Access, Boilermaking, Piping, Industrial Painting, Construction & Assembly and Civil Construction.

Other information

- American Visa valid until 2034
- Winda n.º MD069311
- IRATA n.º 1/20875
- Abraco SNQC-CP n.º 0998